Hey. What's good, Black?
Eh, you know, man.
I'm cooling, man.
-You know,
man. What you been up to, bruh?
Man, I'm running around
like a damn chicken
-with its head cut off, boy.
Yeah, man. You know how it is
at holiday time, man.
-I can't wait for this shit
to be over. -Yeah, man.
Hey, I heard that new song
of yours, man.
That thing fye, though.
Oh, yeah? I appreciate it, fam.
Yeah, man. That shit cool, bruh.
Uh, thanks, man.
Yeah.
Nah, but, for real, man,
you really doing your thing
out here, man.
Like, straight-up, bruh.
Respect, man. Hey, you getting
the same thing, right?
Uh, yeah, man.
Hey, um, I want some
of that molly, too, remember?
-Oh, yeah. It's five
for a ounce. -Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's cool. And I got a...
got the ten in here for that.
-All right, then.
-Hey, nigga. Hey.
Hey, that kush
you gave me last time?
-Yo, that shit was legit, boy.
Oh, yeah?
-What you talking 'bout, that
lemon -Yo.
Yeah, man.
Yo, you got any more of that?
-Nah, I sold all out of that
shit, bruh. -Psh. Damn, man.
I was smoking it my damn self,
man. Let me know when you get
-Yeah, I got you, fam.
Hey, yo, man,
-you ever...
-It ain't my fault, bruh.
Nigga.
I'm sorry about this shit,
bruh. I mean,
you'll be all right though.
You know what I'm saying?
Your song is hot, bruh. Probably
go platinum or some shit.
I ain't making no money
off that fucking song, nigga.
Nigga, calm the fuck down,
nigga.
I need this shit, bruh.
Real talk, man.
Hey, where Darius at, bruh?
He in the car over there?
No, man.
Cool.
Tell him I said, "What's up?"
What?
Hey, let me get your keys,
too, bruh.
I don't want you to chase
after me when I pull off, bruh.
-I don't want you to chase
after me when I pull off, dawg.
Let me get your keys...
Nigga, I heard you.
Shut up, man.
Shit.
Appreciate it, bruh. You can...
you can head out, man.
Child lock, man.
-Hold up. I got you.
-Child lock.
Can you unl... Come on.
Can I get the fuck out, please?
Fuck it, man. I got it.
I got it. I'll just...
I got it. Why you got to
lock in the child?!
Oh, my God.
That's the window, man! St...
Oh, shit...
-BLACK: Hey...
-Whatever, nigga. Whatever.
Hey, I'm sorry about
this shit, man.
Hey, I would take you home, but
you might come out the house
-shooting at me and shit.
-Hey, man.
-Nigga...
I'm-I'm sorry about
this shit, man.
I'm-a pay you back, man.
Appreciate you, man.
*
* Yeah, I just ran through
the bag, it's all there *
* Pull up if you wanna buy
a half, it's all there *
* 28, 36, 1,000,
all there, uh! *
-EARN: Damn, that shit is crazy.
-ALFRED: Ten years.
I been shopping with this nigga
for ten years.
He's just gonna leave me
out there, stranded.
And I had to go back out there
this morning with Darius
to help me pick up my wheels.
You got to be careful, man.
Man, you know the worst part
of it is
is that he done fucked up
my whole shit.
Like-Like, I can't even re-up
and get my money back,
'cause he my plug.
He better hope
I don't catch his ass
out there slippin', boy...
Hey, man, y-you just got off
house arrest.
-You got to be careful with...
-Oh, my God.
Here you go on that
house slave shit, nigga.
I just told you that I almost
lost my life, a'ight?
I at least got to pistol whip
this nigga to death
or some shit.
Fuck out of here!
-EARN: Hi...
-WOMAN: Hi.
EARN:
How are you?
MAN:
You hungry
We got a kitchen
fully stocked for the staff.
It's all organic, you know.
Gluten-free.
-I think we're good. Yeah.
-Yeah.
MAN: Good? All right,
just let me know.
I am in charge
of music outreach here.
My name is Peter Savage,
but everyone here calls me
-"35 Savage," because I'm 35.
MAN 2: We're gonna call you
"36 Savage," soon.
-PETER: All right. Take it easy.
Anyway, we're all big fans
of your music
and your brand here, so we just
want to continue to explore
some opportunities for how
we can grow your reach
through our platform.
-Awesome.
-Cool.
-PETER: Cool.
Yeah, really cool.
All right.
Well, we're excited to hear
what you've been working on,
so let's go ahead
and get that going.
Absolutely. Um...
Here-Here we go.
Uh...
We don't have any disc drives.
Yeah, it's a new
state-of-the-art system.
It's all wireless and fully
integrated into the platform.
How about this? Uh, do you have
it on your phone or laptop?
Yeah. Yeah, actually, I do.
PETER:
All right, great.
Um...
Let's play it from your phone.
If you don't mind,
I'll just...
get on the wireless here.
Yeah.
All right...
E-mail it to me.
Let's do that.
That cool?
-Sure, yeah.
-That'll be easier.
-Let me just...
It's, uh, savagebeast82@hotmail.
I e-mailed you yesterday.
It should...
EARN: Oh, yeah.
You e-mailed me from it...
-Yeah, yeah.
-Um,
you should be getting it...
Okay.
You've got mail.
Just kidding.
No, but I do have it.
Um, let's go... let's go ahead
and let's listen to it.
Uh... Huh.
Okay. Well,
maybe I didn't, uh...
MAN 2:
Let me see.
PETER:
It's saying it's invalid. Okay,
-hey, go grab Ryan for me.
-Yeah.
Yeah, thanks.
Well, see, now it says
it's playing.
Yeah. That doesn't make sense.
-Okay, uh, just play
another track. -Okay.
PETER:
Try another one.
No, see?
That's not working, either.
Um... how 'bout this?
Could we play auxiliary?
MAN 2:
I don't think so.
All right.
-Just give us, like,
ten minutes. -Yeah.
-That'd be cool.
-That'd be good. Yeah.
So, I-I started writing
some music.
This is Paper Boi,
and you're tuned into
the Fresh Mix Rap playlist.
Long live fresh.
-ENGINEER: Okay.
All right, uh...
Let's do another take,
but let's do one... Uh...
Let's do one that's cool,
that's just, like... cool.
This is Paper Boi,
and you're tuned into
the Fresh Rap Mix playlist.
Long live fresh... nigga.
ENGINEER:
Okay. Uh, so,
let's do it again,
and just, like, this time,
like you're at a party, and
everything's crazy.
*
This place, um...
has a vibe.
Hell yeah.
But it's gonna
help you out, man.
I'm super excited.
You're gonna...
you're gonna be happy
you did this.
Yeah, if you say so.
I'll say all that
when I get that check, though.
Yo, what's good?
Paper Boi,
what's happening, man?
* Paper Boi, Paper Boi *
-* All about the paper, boy. *
-ALFRED: Shit.
-Hey.
-Yo, I'm a big fan, bro.
-Yeah, man.
-Appreciate it, man.
-I'm Clark County.
Yeah, I know, man.
Hey, your single, "Money Bags,"
it's, um... it's dope, man.
-Thanks, man, I appreciate that.
-Mm-hmm.
What's up, man?
Oh, yeah, man. This, um.
This my cousin, Earn.
Oh, Cousin Earn.
Cousin Earn, you a rapper, too?
Cousin Earn?
-Nah. I'm-I'm-I'm the manager.
-He's my manager.
Ah, keepin' it in the family.
-I respect that.
-Yeah.
It's nice to see some
black folks up in here, man.
Yo, you know they got a chef
up in here? I got this nigga
-cooking me spaghetti, G.
You know what I'm saying? -Yeah.
-For real, though.
I'm-a get that shit to go, too.
-For real.
Yo, Lucas.
Yo, this is my manager, Lucas.
What's up, Earn?
How you doin', baby?
-Good. I'm good.
-Good to see you.
-Yeah, man, way back in the day.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
What, you're managing now?
-Oh, yeah. I'm managing now.
-Oh, yo,
if he's not taking care of you,
let me know. All right?
-Man.
-Paper Boi,
-they're ready for you.
A'ight? -A'ight.
-Pete Savage.
-Yeah, hey.
-Good to see you, man.
-Good to see you.
-Oh, just hanging, man.
-Yeah, man.
-Yeah, busy day. Yeah.
-It's a nice office, bro.
-Thank you.
-It is. -Thank you, man.
-Living the dream, man.
-I appreciate that. Yeah, yeah.
-Of course, man.
-Yo, you need
some more pictures or something?
-Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Yeah, we can get a couple.
-Yeah. -Yeah, yeah.
-EARN: Uh, no, I'm-I'm good.
-Yeah.
-All right, man. Call me.
-All right. Here we go.
Deuces?
-It's right there.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Deuces.
Where my real niggas at?
Put your hands up.
Yeah.
Man...
("Paper Boi"
instrumental playing)
* Yo *
* Hey *
* Paper... *
* A Hey *
-* Hey, hey, yeah * - Paper
Boi, Paper Boi * - Really *
-* All about that paper, boy *
-* Paper *
-* Got a team to serve it *
-* All from Cali to Decatur,
boy * - Stack it *
* That paper, boy, paper, boy *
-* All about that paper, boy *
-* Yeah *
* I keep a ting *
-* Uh, yeah *
-* Paper Boi... *
TV ANNOUNCER: On the nights
of August 11 through 13...
-DARIUS: Hey.
-DARIUS:
Chillin'. What are we, uh...
Oh, hey. Um...
Got something for you.
What's this?
For the puppies.
Nice little come up.
Oh, shit.
-Ha!
Yo, are you serious?
Yeah, buddy.
Oh, my God. People love dogs.
You know?
* Hey, and it all worked out. *
At least somebody
gettin' paid in this bitch.
Hey, hey now. Don't you worry
your trappin' soul, all right?
We got options coming soon.
And, in fact,
I'm checking on one right now.
We'll probably leave
in a little bit.
Yo, Darius. Thank you so much.
Yo, how much is it, man?
There's like 4K here.
I did not know people
liked dogs this much.
-Hell yeah. -Yo, I could
double that for you.
Uh... No, I'm-I'm good, man.
Man, you better tell your little
cousin to ask about me, man.
Yeah, man. Tracy ain't lying.
He be on them
damn gift cards, man.
Man, you give me the cash,
and I'll double it
on any card you want.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
You know how Al got that TV?
Let's just say it was a steal.
Boy, it's hot up in here, man.
ALFRED:
'Cause of all that damn grease
you got in your scalp, boy.
Whatever, man. Don't hate.
I'm about to have these waves
going crazy
like the Bermuda Triangle, boy.
Nigga, you be acting like
you the king of waves
around here and shit.
I'm the Prince of Tides, nigga.
Man, I got that job interview,
so you know,
I got to be on point.
See, first,
you got to brush it, right?
And then,
you just let them bake.
ALFRED:
Bruh, you ain't the only one
who know how to get no damn
waves. Okay?
TRACY:
Not like these, nigga.
Ooh, yeah.
They baking now, boy.
Ah, man. You always mentioning
these miraculous waves.
-Let me see them.
-Nah, nah. Not yet, man.
I got to leave them undisturbed.
They in the oven right now.
I got to let them bake, baby.
-Yeah.
So, can you double
any amount on any card,
or does it have to be
something like Best Buy?
Man, any store. See,
the mall got these gift cards
for the entire place, man.
I can even do those.
Just give me the cash,
and I'll double it for you.
Oh, you ready to rock?
ALFRED:
Shit, yeah, man. Let's dip.
-Hey, you know, you could just
let me... -Damn, go on, man.
-You always playing with me,
man. -No one will even know.
-Leave, man
-Nobody won't even...
-Quit playing!
-Come on, D-Man.
Yo, get your boy, man!
Hey, I wanted to see them.
-Yeah, damn.
Is there a limit on these?
Nah, no limit.
Matter of fact,
I got to go get some stuff
from the mall, anyway.
So, want to roll?
Yeah, I'll roll.
Cool. Come on, then.
I got to get a pedicure,
anyway, man.
I got them vampire feet.
You know what I'm sayin'?
SHAG: So, I pretty much stay
with some of that, like, always.
The more exotic stuff like that
Skywalker depends, though.
ALFRED:
Yeah, I feel you, man.
Man, the ticket is right
on this, though.
And I can cut you
a better deal depending on
-Yeah, that makes sense, man.
The MDMA shouldn't be a problem
as long as you let me know
how much you want do
from, like, week to week.
All right, yeah.
Oh, oh, the way that smells.
-Yeah, man. That's cool, man.
-Yeah.
-Oh, that's much better. Mm-hmm.
Yo, I'm a fan of your music,
by the way.
Shit's dope.
Thanks, man.
-* Don't wake... *
: Sweet.
-DARIUS: * Don't wake me... *
-Yeah.
Okay, I'm dreamin'.
Hey, yo... Yo, man?
You just take a picture of me?
No.
-Let me get this.
-Yeah, yeah.
You sure your boy cool, man?
Y-Yeah, it's just...
He's a fan.
I told you
he got the juice, man...
Oh.
-Make your eyes water, bruh.
-Oh. Wow.
-This is good, man.
I mean, people want
that loud right here, bruh.
This smell like
my grandma's face.
That's right.
-This is it, right here, man.
Yeah. I think that's the one.
I know it's the one, man.
I can feel it.
Oh...
-Mwah.
-Bruh...
I mean, don't get me wrong,
it's a funny show,
but the way they dive
into depression,
and especially after what
he did to her daughter.
I was like... like,
"Can I even feel bad
for this horse anymore?"
Yo, man, I got to pick up
some shoes
for my job interview today.
Man, hey, yo, you seem
like the preppy type.
Yo, what's a good brand?
Uh, I don't know.
W
I don't know, man,
you just look like the type.
Fuck it.
Yeah, these is what
I'm looking for.
Man, these white people
are gonna love me.
I'm-a get hired on the spot.
Mm.
This is it.
EARN:
So, um...
what kind of job
are you interviewing for?
Some marketing job or some shit.
Yo, they pay, like, 12 an hour.
I'm trying to hit
that lick, boy.
Yo, you went
to Princeton, right?
Yeah.
Man, how should I talk
to these white folk?
Um, I don't know.
Probably don't call them
"white folks,"
and... talk confidently.
A'ight.
A'ight, cool, cool.
Yeah, 'cause, you know,
I'm a talker.
So, um...
Those gift cards,
they work in here?
I don't know.
I'm just gonna take this shit.
Wait, what?
Hell yeah.
They got a no chase policy.
What are you talking about?
BRIAN:
Uh, hello, sir. Uh...
can I help you
find anything today?
They got a no chase policy.
They can't stop me.
Most of these stores got it.
It's a liability thing.
Even if they see me stealing,
they can't chase me.
Um, sir. Those shoes, can I get
you a different size, or...
See. He got to keep giving me
great customer service.
That's all he could do.
Hey, e-excuse me, sir.
Exc...
-*
You high over there, man?
Yeah, man, definitely.
I mean, look, that kush
was legit, though,
man, for real.
Dude, I only smoke
the best shit.
I get it from Humboldt County,
best weed in America.
That's what's up, man.
-Yeah, man.
My uncle--
he's got a farm up there.
Been growing since forever.
Yeah, but how-how much
you do for the pound?
Man, it depends on the strain--
outdoor, indoor-- but for you,
I'll give you a good discount,
'cause I'm a fan.
Well, I mean, like, what you
charge everybody else, though?
Nah, it's cool, bro.
I just got to get a pic
before you go.
I'm just playing.
I'm just playing. You're good.
Yo, I saw you perform
at Dirty Laundry one time.
Me and my girl were in there.
Yeah, she's the one
that put me on to you, bro.
Word? Well, that's cool.
Wait. So your girl
like hippity hop?
Oh, yeah, man.
She's gangsta, bro.
-Gangsta, man.
Yo, I can supply you
with pretty much anything.
Give me your phone number,
and we can link, all right?
I don't really do business over
the phone or anything,
but, you know, we can set up
some meetings or whatever.
*
Hey, man, that tree was fire.
-Shit, I'm still high.
Yeah. Yeah, you are, nigga.
Go to the passenger's side.
Oh, that was...
that's where I was going.
Hey, um...
how you know dude, again?
Oh, that's who our boy Jeff
used to re-up with.
Okay.
* Paper Boi, Paper Boi,
I'm about that paper, boy *
* If you ain't on your grind
and you flexin' *
What the hell?
Yeah, an acoustic rap cover.
Them white girls love that shit.
Yeah, let me see.
ALFRED:
That nigga Andy sent it.
-Nope. Nope.
No, he didn't.
-No, this nigga didn't.
Man, c...
Oh.
(car engine starts,
tires squeal)
How you doing?
You guys, um... take gift cards?
Cool.
Thanks.
(indistinct crowd chatter,
laughter)
*
Where the fuck is this asshole?
He is...
What?
Oh, I'm-a kill this nigga.
I'm gonna kill this...
Shit.
What the hell, nigga?
Man, I had to ride the bus
like this.
Think a old lady
stole my Vitamix, man.
-Damn, man,
that shit is expensive.
I hope you got the, uh,
insurance on it.
Man, Tracy owe me some money.
I didn't even get to spend
the whole $4,000.
And this nigga's stealing,
-right while I'm there,
you know
Good luck getting any of that
damn money back.
-DARIUS: Wait, wait, wait.
-EARN: Yeah.
Right in front of me,
he took a bunch of shoes.
Said something about
a "no-chase policy."
Oh, yeah, he's right about that.
TV ADVERTISER: ...will not
protect or prevent injury...
Well, I hope he's happy.
-Almost got arrested.
Smoke something, man.
Where were you?
I called you, like, six times.
Yeah, um...
I need a new phone.
DARIUS:
Oh, look at this dude.
This Clark County dude,
-he making money, man.
-* Hey, hey *
-* I flex on the bitch like *
-* Yoo-hoo *
-* I just got shit like *
* Haters gonna hate like uh
till they see me in the face *
-* Then they all like *
-* Yoo-hoo *
-* Saw your baby mama like *
* And then I sent her home
with a good night *
* Bottle's in his hands
like good night *
* And we drink Yoo-hoo
like it's dirty Sprite *
-* Yeah *
-Aw, I hate this shit.
* Yoo-hoo, yoo-hoo, yoo-hoo... *
-Man...
-* Yoo-hoo, yoo-hoo, yoo-hoo *
Shit is good.
* Yoo-hoo, yoo-hoo,
yoo-hoo, yoo-hoo. *
Yeah.
I mean, that might be
a big gap in my résumé,
but, you know,
I think I could be
a big help to this
organization here.
How you doing?
All right.
I think that might be
my biggest weakness,
because I love learning.
-MAN: Mm.
You cannot stop me
from learning.
Like, every day I'm looking for
something new to learn.
Well, I think you have
a lot of potential.
TRACY:
Huh.
Yeah. Yeah.
Unfortunately...
I don't think we'll be able to
offer you a job here right now.
It... We're just fully staffed
at the moment.
Man, fuck y'all.
Y'all racist as hell
up in here, man!
Fuck you want from me, man?
Get some black people
up in here,
that's your motherfucking
problem, boy.
-Shit.
: I don't want
to work for you anyway.
-Ameri-KKK, nigga!
AMBER:
* Paper Boi, Paper Boi *
* I'm about that paper, boy *
* If you ain't on your grind *
* And you flexin',
you's a hater, boy *
* Paper Boi, Paper Boi *
* I'm about that paper, boy *
* If you ain't makin' money *
* Then you ain't
a money maker, boy *
* Paper clip, paper clip *
* I'm-a need a paper clip *
* I'm stacking up this paper *
* So you know I'll make
this paper flip *
* Paper flip, paper flip *
* I'm-a make this paper flip *
* Then head to Magic City *
* And I bet this paper
make her strip *
* Paper man, paper man *
* I'll be in the paper, man *
* Like Wall Street Journal,
yeah *
* 'Cause I'll be
gettin' paper, man *
* Paper man, paper man *
* I'll be gettin' paper, man *
* Ooh-ooh *
* Yeah. *
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH